fleetfarm.com 2011-06-11

# Mills Fleet Farm -Online Store Privacy Policy

### Mills’ Respect For Privacy

Mills e-Commerce Enterprises, Inc. d/b/a Mills Fleet Farm (“Mills”) respects the importance of the privacy of your personal information. Mills provides this Privacy Policy so you know about Mills’ online information practices and understand how Mills treats the information we receive about you from your use of the Mills’ online store (the “Site”). By using, browsing and/or accessing the Site, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy. Your visit to the Site and any dispute over privacy is subject to the Terms of Use, including limitations on damages and application of the law of the state of Minnesota. Use of this Site is strictly voluntary. If you do not agree to the Site’s Privacy Policy and Terms of Use, you must immediately log off the Site and may not use the Site.

### The Information Mills Collects

In general, you can browse this Site without telling Mills who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. Mills, however, collects your IP address. Your IP address is a number that is used by computers connected to the Internet to identify your computer so that data (such as the Web pages you request) can be sent to you. Mills uses your IP address to, among other things,: (1) help diagnose problems with Mills’ server; administer the Site; measure the use of the Site; improve the content of the Site; (2) identify visitors' domain names, the type of web browsers used, the pages viewed, the web sites from which a visitor found this Site, the search terms and search engines used to find this Site; and (3) gather other web analytics information relating to visitors’ use and navigation of the Site. This information does not identify you personally. On occasion Mills may aggregate this data with data on the pages visited by other users to track overall visitor traffic patterns and provide this aggregate information to vendors, potential advertisers, business partners, news agencies, or other parties to demonstrate the amount of interest in the Site and to help Mills plan for technical infrastructure requirements.

In order to register on or purchase items from the site your browser must be set to accept Cookies. Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that Mills transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable the Site to "recognize" you every time you visit and to "remember" any information you have saved, such as storage of items in your shopping cart between visits. Mills does not use cookies to store any of your personal or financial information that you have on your computer.

Mills recognizes that you have a choice to refuse cookies. However, should you decide not to accept cookies from the Site, you will limit the functionality Mills can provide when you visit the Site. View your browser's help file for more information on cookies.

Mills receives and may store information you enter on the Site or give to our Site in any other way. For example, Mills collects information you provide when you place an order or register to create an account on the Site. The information may include, without limitation, your first and last name, mailing address, email address, telephone and facsimile numbers, credit card information, and other personal identifying information. If you choose to share any personal information with Mills, you will see that the amount and type of personal information Mills requests depends on how you use the Site. It is completely optional for you to engage in these activities. Depending upon the activity, some of the information Mills asks you to provide is identified as mandatory and some is voluntary. If you do not provide the mandatory information with respect to a particular activity, you will not be able to engage in that activity.

### The Way Mills Uses Personal Information

Mills may use your personal information for particular activities, including, without limitation, processing your order; credit card processing; collections; returns management; manufacturing; storage; shipping; delivery; fulfillment; customer service; marketing and research; providing product, promotional and other information to you; and to contact you regarding administrative notices. Mills may share this information with Mills’ affiliates, dealers or other business partners in connection with any of the foregoing activities. Mills’ affiliates, dealers or other business partners may use this information for marketing and solicitation purposes. Mills must release your credit card information to credit card authorization service providers and Mills’ credit card-acquiring (merchant) bank to process your payment for products or services purchased on this Site and to facilitate returns or refunds. Except as described above, Mills will not give or sell your personal information to any other company for its use in marketing or solicitation.

Mills may disclose personal information in any of the following circumstances: (1) in response to a subpoena, search warrant, court order, or other legal process or request, or as may otherwise be required by applicable law or regulation; (2) to protect and defend Mills’ rights or property or those of its affiliates, dealers, business partners, or others; or (3) as Mills, in its sole discretion, believes is appropriate under exigent circumstances in response to a perceived threat to the personal safety, property, or rights of any other person or organization.

In addition, since Mills’ database is a business asset, in the event Mills is reorganized or is sold to or merged with another company, you consent to the sale, assignment, or transfer of your personal information to a purchaser of all or substantially all of Mills’ business assets, or to an affiliate, as applicable.

Mills will never request your password, user name, credit card information or other personal information through e-mail. This practice, called “phishing,” is a scam designed to steal your personal information. If you receive an e-mail that looks like it is from Mills asking you for your personal information, do not respond.

### Mills’ Relationship to Other Sites that can be Accessed Through this Site

This Site may contain links to other web sites. Additionally, other web sites may contain links to this Site. Mills does not review or monitor the web sites linked to this Site and is not responsible for the contents or privacy policies related to any other web sites. If you visit one of these other web sites, you may want to review the privacy policy on that web site. Where this Site contains a link to another web site owned and/or operated by Mills, such web site use may be subject to different and additional terms of use and privacy policy terms and conditions.

### Access and Correction of your Personal Information

Mills strives to maintain the accuracy and integrity of the personal information in its databases and to keep that information up-to-date. Mills encourages you to promptly update your personal information if it changes.

You may request access to the personal information Mills has about you. As a registered user with the Site, you can access your profile information at any time. If you prefer, you may email us, or send a letter to:

Mills e-Commerce Enterprises, Inc.

Attention: MFF Customer Service Department

14858 Dellwood Drive, Suite 200

Baxter, MN 56425

All communications must be in the English language.

Mills will respond to reasonable requests within the time limits established by applicable law or within a reasonable time if no time limit is established by applicable law. For your protection, Mills may ask you for additional information to verify your identity. In most cases, Mills will provide the access you request and correct or delete any inaccurate personal information you discover. Mills reserves the right, however, to limit or deny your request to the extent permitted by applicable law if: (1) the disclosure may be threat to the personal safety, property, or rights of any other person or organization; (2) the disclosure may lead to a violation of applicable laws or regulations; or (3) where you have failed to provide sufficient evidence to verify your identity.

### Security of Your Personal Information

Mills takes what it believes to be reasonable precautions and has implemented managerial and technical procedures to try to protect the security of data and information, including personal information. Mills strives to maintain the reliability, accuracy, completeness, and current status of personal information and to protect the privacy and security of such. Mills cannot guarantee against any loss, misuse, unauthorized disclosure, alteration or destruction of data or personal information. While Mills strives to protect your personal information, Mills cannot guarantee the security of any information you transmit to or from this Site, by email or otherwise, and you provide such information at your own risk. You acknowledge that: (1) there are security and privacy limitations in computer systems and on the Internet which are beyond Mills’ control; (2) the security, integrity, and privacy of any and all information and data exchanged between you and Mills through the Site, including personal information, cannot be guaranteed; and (3) any such information and data, including personal information, may be viewed or tampered with by a third party while such information or data is being used, transmitted, processed, or stored.

### Changes to Privacy Policy

Mills reserves the right to modify this Privacy Policy, in whole or in part, at any time without notice to you. You expressly waive any right to receive notice of any changes to this Privacy Policy. Mills encourages you to review this Privacy Policy regularly in your use of the Site to ensure you are aware of current practices. Any use of the Site following the date on which Mills implements changes to this Privacy Policy shall constitute your acceptance of all such changes. This policy was last updated on March 25, 2009

© Mills e-Commerce Enterprises, Inc. 2011 - All Rights Reserved.
